Close enough lore fallout 4's backstory. Honestly, I bought fallout 4 for the competitive multiplayer, but Todd forgot to add it
I tried the single player, but I don't understand why was there a nuclear war?
so I researched it using a scientific method. Fallout 4 takes place in an alternate reality in the year 2287 back in the
2050s the Planet started to run out of
Energy because unlike the real world you can't get as much energy as you want from those holes in the wall so China invaded Alaska
but that was just a prank (Gone Wrong) (Gone Sexual)
So they gave up. Europe had become a unified country did you know that Europeans invented a spiral staircase?
That's it though
That is why the eu flag is a spiral staircase, but they are missing a few stars
But one country didn't join and they saw an opportunity
In this energy crisis. If the world is destroyed by nukes we can build a better world a
Norwegian World Meanwhile in the Oval office
Hmm. I'm going to try my best to sound like a native English speaker oi vice we built 122 vaults yeah? can they fit all
four hundred million people. No, are you mental one can fit like a thousand people? We need at least 200
Hello. It's me the prime minister of China at least I think it's prime minister the important thing
Is that we are declaring war against you and your greatest ally norway there was no turning back now
The Norwegian prime minister has already spent ten times
norway's GDP on 300 Square meters of butter and
Studies show that only four out of ten Norwegians would support that. There are these things called vaults?
But in the first fallout game you only spend like 40 minutes in one so they are clearly not important
But in Boston Maschusuade when the bomb started to fall our protagonist hid in one of these vaults Maysasuchechets
mez nice shoes
Are these even real places? Why are we the games never in places people have actually been oh? Yeah?
Then everything exploded and everything got destroyed except for of course
Norway they managed to absorb the radiation by building giant butter walls if you come in contact with heavy doses of radiation
Just smear yourself in butter and laugh at all the people panicking. The Norwegians kept happy behind these walls for a hundred years
But because of their absence their most ancient
enemy had grown in numbers and in power in
2177 the Norwegians received a grim reminder
Wait a minute if Boston is a real city. Do they have real-life framerate issues